[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "How do they keep it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "You know, that's a great question because I don't know if I'm wired that way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "You know, I think it's effort.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Did you just go party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Like a madman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$13 million", "$18 million", "$25 million"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CD", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", ",", "RB", "$", "CD", "CD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", ":", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What was -- what were the revenues in your company when you sold it for $5.9 billion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "We were doing -- well, we were doing about 20 -- well, the last public quarter, I think, was $13 million, then $18 million, then I think our -- last one after we sold was $25 million for the quarter.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$5.9 billion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Have you done that throughout your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "You seem to always say, where's the next edge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "WRB", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Because those guys get it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "That part is not hard because once you taste it, I mean, you just got to go back for more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Are we better off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Where are we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Individually, it just depends on your own personal circumstances that you may or may not be better off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "IN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "You were telling me during the break, what did you say about the ring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, my ring, I can't have it out where I can see it because I just get so fired up and like, so crazy, like let's go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "What did it mean to you to create that victory with a team after a little less than 10 years, a little more than 10 years, I guess?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "You know, it's hard to describe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "And it's always more of a relief than anything else, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "And what would your report card be for what you think Mitt Romney can do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Well, first of all, I'm not a big supporter of anybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "If the Internet hadn't happened for President Clinton, he doesn't have a surplus, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "So how would you rate the parties?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "They both scare the hell out of me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "And we say, OK, what are you going to do to increase profits for this company?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "And you're willing to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Oh, I always do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "What's a kid supposed to do in a spot like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Would you share an example of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "The notion that a single person, acting alone without anybody watching, can change the course of an enterprise is probably true as much for a company as it is for a country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Is there a conflict between spirituality and economic success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I -- I don't think, I think the answer to that is now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "And if you obviously feel differently, why and what do we need to do to move America forward to start growing again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", ",", "WRB", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Well, it was fun to meet Mark Cuban and to be here with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Romney"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "What's going to get them back in the game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "What President Romney can do, we've got -- what we've got in the White House today is a first-rate campaigner and a great speechmaker.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2700"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "What would you change?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Any bill that's 2700 pages, when you -- if you're a citizen and you're looking at this television program, I'm going to make an intemperate statement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Is that your concern?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "YNN: If we take a break --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["All State", "Geico"], "PERSON": ["Tony"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RBS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "WRB", ":", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Right now under the Obama the prices are increasing for your employees, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "Tony, Tony, when they take a break at CNN, most likely, you're going to see an argument between Progressive, All State and Geico on how -- on how to get cheaper auto insurance.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "You did this with your own company, did you not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Culinary Union"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "You cut, what, a $1,000 fee from an MRI down to what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", ",", "DT", "$", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "TO", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "I got -- I got with my union, the Culinary Union.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "You're 84 now, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "You're the greatest person I could put out there to dispel it, but how can you help people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "ICKENS: I still have a lot of things to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "That helps, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "And I'm running out of time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1969"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "How did you do that and why are you so focused on health care?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "Putting in a fitness center in 1969.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["four years ago"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "What's the plan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "The -- I started this four years ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "OBBINS: You've got 51 votes, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Transportation Bill"]}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "So why didn't it get passed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Well, this was an amendment to the Transportation Bill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "You're following this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "No, I'm not, but I get the idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "They played with the rules, so you had to get 60 votes instead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "Well, they voted it non-germane, and I got 51.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 748, "question": "So, really, we have more natural gas now than Saudi Arabia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "We have -- you think --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Saudi Arabia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Has oil?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "We have more natural gas than any country in the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", ",", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "Why doesn't President Obama step in and say, we're going to take all of the vehicles the US government has and put them on natural gas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "That's just 200,000, is what it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["US"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Won't it lead by example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "No, but it - exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "Most people are not good at -- most people are not good at changing their styles, how are they going to change their entire culture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "RBS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 821, "question": "Scalability?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 822, "answer": "Well, just because we have the most brains of any country in the world and that we're innovating more rapidly --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "Steve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "Just listen to these two guys is how.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 843, "question": "As opposed to private enterprise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 844, "answer": "He has an energy policy that would be successful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "What is America's greatest strength going forward?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "Our people.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 860, "question": "What do we have to look forward to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 861, "answer": "Individual initiative, greed, the sense to do better in life, to have a better life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120916pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Mark, is government going to do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "This conversation is going to continue after we continue to roll, I have a feeling here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]